a matter of figuring it out, just
getting into groove. What clicked for
you at last year um to earn this deal?
>> Yeah. Um you know, like you said, it's
it's a tough business
um as a kicker in this league and um you
just got to kind of you know, learn to
to have a short memory and you know, be
able to move on to the next kick. And
you know, I think coming here and you
know, kind of having a a nice reset was
a good thing. And um you know being in a
specialist room with with Tres and Tyler
Aught and having a good coach uh like
coach Isizo, it's you know it helps a
lot um to build you know not only
confidence but you know even some things
with you know your technique and stuff
you know picking up stuff from you know
vets like that. It's it's pretty helpful
and you know I'm very glad to to be in a
group you know like the one that's here.
Was there anything in terms of technique
that maybe that that helped you or was
it just anything in particular?
>> Uh nothing specifically
um like technical wise, but more so
maybe like mentally just kind of slowing
myself down and um you know kind of
taking each kick as its own thing and um
kind of like I mentioned earlier just
moving on to the next kick no matter
what whether you make or miss. Um, you
know, the the most important kick is the
next one. So, not getting too high after
a make or not getting too low after a
miss. You got to like always kind of
stay nice and flat.
>> Nikki,
>> hi Jake. Um,
we've talked to players over the years
and where they go training and
everything and we've seen some of the
clips obviously on social media, but
where do you where do you go? Where do
you find space to pick?
>> Uh, so for the off season, you know,
I've been staying back home in Michigan.
Uh, fortunately, I grew up very close to
the University of Michigan. Um, so I'm
only about 25 minutes down the road from
there. Um, so I've I've been kicking um,
in the indoor. Obviously, you don't want
to be kicking outside in the winter in
Michigan, but um and I've had, you know,
my former uh snapper and holder as well.
They've been in Michigan helping me out.
Um Brad Robbins and uh Greg Tar and
William Wagner who's also uh a snapper
in the NFL. He's, you know, he's always
around from time to time. So having a
good group of guys like that to train
with and you know the best of the best
facilities um it's it's pretty cool
having that just down the road.
>> And when you talk about um improvement
as a kicker I mean how do how do you
approach that in the offseason? How do
you continually improve? Is that just
you know finding consistency or is there
something else?
Yeah, it's um you know, at this point in
my career, you know, I feel like I'm not
really going to get, you know, too much
stronger necessarily or anything like
that. You know, I'm not I'm not trying
to add distance to my kicks anymore.
It's it's whatever you can find like the
little bits of, you know, how to get
more consistent. Um you know, whether
that be, you know, with my steps, my
approach,
um you know, ball contact, stuff like
that. It's it's pretty similar to to a
golfer, you know, the going to the
driving range and working on certain
swing thoughts and stuff like that. It's
I would, you know, say it's it's very
similar to that.
>> Ben,
>> hey, congrats. um you know in terms of
the prep prepping for the in the
offseason with the way that the the
they've changed how you guys are allowed
to manipulate the balls I guess but
during you know before games how do you
factor that into what you do at home?
>> Yeah. Um, so I guess it it actually
plays uh better, you know, to what most
people have at home. Um, you know, from
kicking a bunch and uh the balls hitting
against, you know, pavement or the balls
hitting against like the the big glass
windows inside of uh Michigan's indoor.
You know, my balls are all pretty broken
in and beat up. So, uh, you know, now
that we can actually use some more
broken in footballs and games and stuff
that actually plays, you know, a lot
nicer, uh, you know, in comparison to
what I've been practicing with because
it it's hard to, you know, you know, buy
a set of three new footballs every
single time you you want to kick in the
off season to kind of replicate the old,
you know, rules. But, yeah, so I I would
say it's uh it's a little bit better
now.
Nice. And you know, um, obviously the
roster is not out of your control, but
did they give you any sense of if there
will be any other kickers and camper?
You kind of have a sense that it's going
to be, you know, you out there. Uh,
>> I couldn't tell you. You know, not not
my decision to make or anything like
that. But, um, you know, I'm I'm happy
that, you know, I'll have a chance to at
least, you know, compete for a job if if
that's the case. And if not, um, you
know, obviously still going to work my
tail off and, um, do the best I can to
to play this upcoming season.
>> Great. Thanks. Congrats again.
>> Thank you.
>> Anybody else?
>> All right. Thanks, Jake.
>> Thanks, guys.